생물학적으로 너보다 어린 나이에 58살이야
who was biologically younger than you are, and he's 58.
마이 스페이스 친구.
MySpace guy.
그래서 무슨 일이 일어나고 있는 거지?
So what is going on?
어...이건 클라우드 서비스 구성입니다.
Uh... It's this cloud service configuration,
일주일 넘게 매달려 있었어요
I've been stuck on it for over a week. - Wow.
저는 훌륭한 프로그래머입니다. 내 말은, 그게 내가 잘하는 유일한 것이라는 거야.
I'm a good programmer. I mean, it's the only thing I am good at.
작년에 프리스비를 던졌더니 이가 부러졌어요
I mean, last year, I threw a Frisbee and it chipped my tooth.
그것은 치과 문제에 더 가까워요.
That's more of a dental issue.
그래, 알았어, 난...
Yup, OK, I...
중요한 건, 제가 17살 때 주말에 루비 onRails를 배웠어요.
The point is, I learned Ruby on Rails over a weekend when I was 17.
클라우드를 배울 수 있어야 합니다.
I should be able to learn cloud, I have to.